

Profile

Enthusiastic and dedicated coder, problem solver with experience in embedded systems, deployment(Docker), network administrations & security and full-stack web development. Highly adaptable professional with a commitment to all aspects of coding languages and the promotion of growth. Demonstrated skills in PHP-, HTML, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL, PostgreSQL, C, and a passionate learner of NodeJS, EJS, React, and many more.

Education

Computer Programming, Hive Helsinki, Helsinki

OCTOBER 2021 - PRESENT

In Hive, we learn to learn efficiently, solve problems, and grow our teamwork skills.

Peer-to-peer studies shaping the next generation of coders.

Skills solidified: project collaboration, interpersonal communication, rigor, and personal responsibility.

Interesting projects for which I am proud:

- The first fifty most important function recreation in C <u>Libft</u>.
- Dockering, creating my own Minecraft containerized server Docker.
- My <u>proudest</u> project so far is made solo, full-stack a re-creation of Instagram, fully functional and live! <u>CHECK OUT</u>

A2 finnish language skill, SataEdu, Rauma

JANUARY 2017 - DECEMBER 2018

After the course, I continued to grow my knowledge and get a higher level (B2) of Finnish speaking.

Construction Technician, Schulek Frigyes Bilingual Technical Secondary and High School, Budapest

JANUARY 2011 - DECEMBER 2016

Employment History

Scaffolder, TekijäRent, Espoo

NOVEMBER 2020 - OCTOBER 2021

Responsibilities to scaffold Länsimetro Soukka stop, team-management & storage management.

Housekeeper, Kotipalvelu Ykköset, Espoo

AUGUST 2019 - JUNE 2020

Helped to increase customer return rates by providing excellent customer service at all times.

Founder of Lumundoo, Self-employer, Espoo

DECEMBER 2018 - DECEMBER 2019

Established my own drop-shipping business. Responsibility for customer care and service, website & storage management, Commercial and collaboration with influencers. Coordinated mailings, marketing materials, and website content. First taste of coding a website.

Final-cleaner, Enersense International Oyj/VMP Oy, Rauma

AUGUST 2017 - JUNE 2018

Responsibilities of the nuclear power-plant final-cleaning, and maintaining that.

Ship-designer(internship), Deltamarin, Rauma

FEBRUARY 2017 - MAY 2017

Adapt in short time to new technologies like AutoCAD.

Details

Espoo Finland +35844-989-4822 gaborulenius@gmail.com

Links

My Portfolio Mangofruit GitHub Linkedin

Machine Languages

PHP C

HTML

MySQL, PostgreSQL

CSS

JavaScript

NodeJS

React

Skills

Teamwork

Creative Problem Solving

Adaptability

Communication

Customer Service

Efficiency

Time management

Organization & rigor

Tools

VirtualStudio
Docker
GitHub, Gitlab & Git
Terminal, Termux
Linux
Vim, Nano
Asana
MAMP, XAMPP, LAMP
MyphpAdmin, pgAdmin,
DataGrip
Postman